[{"body": [{"title": "尺子输入框", "stem": "按照顺序填一填", "content": ["0", "1", "2"], "number": "1-1-8-05", "type": "rule-number", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": ["0", "1", "2"], "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-8-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "尺子输入框", "stem": "按照顺序填一填", "content": ["0", "1", "3"], "number": "1-1-8-05", "type": "rule-number", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": ["0", "1", "3"], "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-8-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "尺子输入框", "stem": "按照顺序填一填", "content": ["0", "1", "4"], "number": "1-1-8-05", "type": "rule-number", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": ["0", "1", "4"], "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-8-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "尺子输入框", "stem": "按照顺序填一填", "content": ["0", "1", "5"], "number": "1-1-8-05", "type": "rule-number", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": ["0", "1", "5"], "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-8-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "尺子输入框", "stem": "按照顺序填一填", "content": ["0", "2", "3"], "number": "1-1-8-05", "type": "rule-number", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": ["0", "2", "3"], "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-8-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "尺子输入框", "stem": "按照顺序填一填", "content": ["0", "2", "4"], "number": "1-1-8-05", "type": "rule-number", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": ["0", "2", "4"], "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-8-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "尺子输入框", "stem": "按照顺序填一填", "content": ["0", "2", "5"], "number": "1-1-8-05", "type": "rule-number", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": ["0", "2", "5"], "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-8-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "尺子输入框", "stem": "按照顺序填一填", "content": ["0", "3", "4"], "number": "1-1-8-05", "type": "rule-number", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": ["0", "3", "4"], "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-8-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "尺子输入框", "stem": "按照顺序填一填", "content": ["0", "3", "5"], "number": "1-1-8-05", "type": "rule-number", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": ["0", "3", "5"], "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-8-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "尺子输入框", "stem": "按照顺序填一填", "content": ["0", "4", "5"], "number": "1-1-8-05", "type": "rule-number", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": ["0", "4", "5"], "knowledges": ["0的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-8-05"}]